Here we go.
Will it stay on?
-Stick it on the body. Hold it.
-Attach it…
JUST ATTACH IT
Careful.
-Why is it so weird?
-It's not quite a head.
A CHICKEN COMB?
-Looks ridiculous.
-Gotta fine-tune this.
-That's ugly.
-Oh, don't let it fall!
Is it an animal?
Oh, man.
Yeah, that's bizarre.
Maybe we can round it out.
Okay.
ENDLESS CHOP CHOP
Wow, that snowman is huge.
-It's so impressive.
-It's the biggest snowman ever.
A GIANT SNOWMAN TALLER THAN A PERSON
EXCITED
Hey, the head's getting bigger.
Stop adding more and more snow.
The head is gonna fall off soon.
I can't help it, I'm being greedy.
I want it to be even bigger.
I can't control myself,
I'm getting carried away.
Call it, it looks good.
-It's huge.
-Needs more snow.
You're gonna ruin it.
-It's time to call it.
-Add more, add more.
-Oh, God.
-No, hey! Come on, now.
I'LL ADD IT TO YOU
How dare you? You're gonna pay!
They're fighting again. Uh-oh, guys.
RUNNING AWAY
WANTING MORE
Hey, try hitting this… Baseball.
BASEBALL?
I'M DOWN
The shovel's my bat.
CELEBRATION
EARPLUGS AND NOSE PLUGS ACQUIRED
THE PART-TIMER JOINS THE OWNER
That moment when we were jumping
around like frogs felt really magical.
I wanna make a snow angel.
Jun-ho, take a picture of me?
ZUHA TOO
They're good. I'll send them to you both.
We have to do the thing.
The angel. Snow angel.
FLAP
Like this?
Dude. Dude.
Now I'm getting hot.
Good job, guys. Let's go in?
-All right.
-Let's go.
Huh?
What?
Oh…
THIS SOUND
I guess more people are coming today.
-Hello?
-Yes, hello?
Hi. I'm hoping to check in today.
Okay.
IT'S REALLY A GUEST
And what time is best for us
to arrive at the B&B?
-Uh, let's say, 4:00 p.m.?
-Sure.
Yeah, we'll see you soon.
I'll send you the address.
-Okay. Thanks.
-How many people?
-There are two of us.
-We're just two people.
-Okay. All right, great.
-Yeah.
TWO MALE GUESTS
-They're coming now?
-I guess.
Someone's coming for the last night.
-Should we hold this pose?
-Feels so good.
-I love this.
-It's incredible!
This is once in a lifetime.
They don't have this in Seoul.
-Okay.
-Feels good?
-It totally does.
-Am I doing this right?
-I want to have good alignment.
-And, one.
My gosh, this view is one-of-a-kind.
Where is the house? I don't see it.
THEY HEAD TO KIAN'S B&B
GROCERIES
Here we go.
Here, I'll lift them up.
Let's use the tray.
I got it.
THE TRAY PULLEY SYSTEM HE MADE YESTERDAY
-We'll attach all this.
-Oh…
You good?
-Wow.
-Cool.
Okay. I'll organize things up here
and come down.
They said they're here at 4:00?
We should close this. Let's hide it.
PREPARING FOR THE LAST GUESTS
We need to make the welcome drinks.
Last ones.
THE LAST WELCOME DRINKS
Should we put out the cabbage
and omelet to make it cute?
FOOD DECORATION FOR THE GUESTS
LIKE A WELL-OILED MACHINE
Everyone's so chill right now.
How do you all stay so calm?
We've learned how to relax.
We've already hosted so many guests.
How many is it now, 30 people?
You're basically pros.
We're almost there.
THE LAST GUESTS ARRIVE
Wow. I can't believe
there's a house all the way out here.
It's really huge, huh?
Think they'll be able
to open the door for us?
KNOCK
One sec.
"Welcome…" Okay.
IS EVERYTHING READY?
EVERYONE'S READY
THEN
THE PART-TIMER IS ALSO READY
FOR THE CEREMONY
Okay, here we go.
-Hello.
-Hi, come in!
-Welcome! Step inside
-This is so cool.
We've been waiting for you guys
-So nice to meet you both
-What's happening?
Our youngest staff
-wishes you a warm welcome.
-Hello!
Zuha, Zuha, Kazuha!
Welcome!
Hi, guys, hi, guys!
Oh, shoot. I hit him. Sorry.
Glad you made it. I have something.
A WELCOME DRINK TO MAKE UP FOR THE HIT
-Thank you.
-It's a lemon detox drink.
ZING
And we have Dex,
who will be preparing our dinner for us.
So great to see you all.
You've traveled so far!
-Oh, wow. That's amazing.
-Nice to meet you.
PART-TIMER GOES BACK TO PREPARING DINNER
-Welcome!
-Nice to meet you.
Welcome. Can I have your name?
-I'm Mun Hyeon-jun.
-Mr. Hyeon-jun.
-And I'm Park Ui-jin.
-Ui-jin.
So, uh, what do you guys do for a living?
I play video games professionally.
-Whoa, are you serious?
-What game do you play?
-League of Legends.
-Oh, really?
Yeah, I'm actually a player for T1.
-T1?!
IN A HURRY
You're T1 players?
Yes, Hyeon-jun is a pro T1 player.
LEAGUE OF LEGENDS
A GAME LOVED ALL AROUND THE WORLD
T1
A TEAM THAT REPRESENTS KOREA
CORE MEMBER OF T1
ONER
MUN HYEON-JUN
Wow, I'm such a giant fan!
And I do commentary for the games,
basically a content streamer.
FORMER T1 PRO GAMER
CURRENTLY A GAME STREAMER
-Oh, commentary?
-Cool.
What brought you all the way here
for just one night?
My schedule is tight,
I didn't have the time off,
but we wanted to come to relax for a bit.
Even for one day?
-Well, cool.
-We made it.
Yeah. Make yourselves at home.
Put your things down, look around.
-We're back.
-Welcome back!
-How did it go?
-We had a really good time.
Hello, please open the door!
-We're back!
-Hey. You're all good?
Are our little cuties back home?
-Hi.
-We made it back.
-Meet our new guests.
-Hello.
-Hi.
-How's it going?
-Nice to meet you.
-Hello.
WAIT
Could that really be…
-Gosh, I think they're from T1!
-Are they T1?
Oh, excuse me,
are you guys League players for T1?
Oh, yes, yes, we are.
Holy crap!
BACKING AWAY IN AWE
They recognized them right away.
-Oh… Oh, my goodness!
-I know!
Cute.
-It's such an honor.
-Oh, my God, I'm flattered.
Great to meet you.
IMPROMPTU FAN MEETING
Welcome.
I love T1. I'm a huge fan.
-You like League of Legends?
-Such a fan.
Yes, I play it a ton.
And watch you play it.
I can't believe
I'm meeting you in real life.
I never would have imagined
meeting them here.
I was really honored and excited.
What a crazy, awesome surprise.
MEANWHILE THE OWNER
Maybe it could still be bigger…
Yeah, this is my last chance.
Wait, what are you doing?
The snowman needs a little more.
-Huh?
-You're working on the snowman?
Yeah, it keeps calling out to me
to add to it.
GET OVER HERE OWNER
-I'll be back.
-Okay.
These stairs are such a brilliant idea.
HMM
Yeah, it's not tall enough.
STARTING TO MAKE THE SNOWMAN TALLER
PILING THE SNOW HIGHER THAN HIS HEIGHT
TOSSES THE SHOVEL
PATTING IT DOWN CAREFULLY
Is it even?
UGH
OOF
URGH
PACK PACK PACK
That's kinda cute.
ROUNDING OUT THE BASE
Oh, no!
A COMPLETE MESS
Oh, shit.
Oh, no.
THE HEAD GOES MISSING
CRUMBLES
Oh, shit. I shouldn't have been greedy.
Keep that up and you'll lose the head.
Shit.
SNAP
NOTHING IS GOING THE OWNER'S WAY
I totally brought this on myself.
Why is this shovel so flimsy?
GRABBING A NEW SHOVEL
Dang it.
SHAKY
TOSSES THE SHOVEL
FIRST SECURING THE HEAD AGAIN BY HAND
Gentle touches, gentle touches.
Don't fall apart.
If you fall apart again, it's over.
ADDING MORE SNOW
CROWN MASSAGE
LET'S SEE
RESTORATION COMPLETE?
If only it hadn't fallen apart,
it would've been such a sight to behold.
Oh, man.
That's commitment.
-Great work.
-How was it out there?
COMPLETELY DRAINED
-What happened?
-You're exhausted.
Oh, the head fell off. The whole top.
-Huh?
-Huh? It fell off?
-You should've told us!
-I mean, I put it back on.
-What?
-Why didn't you tell us?
I should fix my own mistakes.
It landed on me like…
-The head was too heavy.
-The entire head.
-You hurt?
-I know, I should have.
-He's upset about the snowman's head.
-It fell off.
Just got really obsessed with it.
READING THE ROOM
Is anyone bored right now?
You can be honest.
US?
-You guys want to build a snowman?
-Another one?
It'll be fun. I had a blast building mine.
Wanna build one next to mine?
-We could have a contest.
-Let's go together. Right now.
-Okay.
-All right.
-Shall we?
-Let's go.
Am I gonna be freezing in only this?
Maybe red would be good for the eyes?
BELL PEPPERS ACQUIRED
CUCUMBER ACQUIRED
-Here we go.
-It's freezing.
THE SNOWMAN CREW HEADS OUT
Oh, wow. That's big.
-We just need to beat Kian's.
-This is a great spot here.
Let's go.
BUILDING IT NEXT TO THE STAFF'S SNOWMAN
You think yours can be bigger than ours?
No question.
Is the base big enough?
Let's just gather the snow first.
-Pile it here?
-Here?
-Yeah.
-Oh, yeah. We got this.
This is great cardio.
-Just pile it up.
-Okay.
THE OWNER ALSO KEEPS ADDING TO IT
Let's make it fatter.
PAT PAT
Almost back to where it was.
PATTING IT CAREFULLY WITH HIS HANDS
This is a competitive group.
-We're all in on height.
-Great job, you guys. Okay.
The more you do this,
the more addictive it becomes.
-You guys tired?
-Oops.
OH COME ON
-Haven't even warmed up.
-Just getting started.
-You guys tired?
-Oh, no way.
PAT PAT PAT PAT PAT
There, good as new.
THE SNOWMAN'S GOTTEN EVEN BIGGER
It's looking really tall.
-Great!
-It's pretty big already.
-Really?
-Yeah.
-We already win on height.
-Really?
-We caught up.
-Oh, good.
-Can I share my opinion?
-Huh?
It looks like a giant, white turd.
I think it looks like ice cream.
Soft serve.
-That's a nicer description.
-You're not wrong.
-This is fun.
-So much fun.
I've never enjoyed
playing in the snow this much.
ENJOYING WINTER TO THE FULLEST
AT KIAN'S B&B
Gonna make you handsome.
THE SNOWMAN'S GOTTEN PRETTIER
Okay, we still need to finish strong.
-Oh, yeah.
-Wow.
You like it?
PLOPPING DOWN
Wow. They built that thing fast.
-It's looking good.
-Not bad.
-Good work.
-Good job, team.
-I feel so proud.
-Good job.
You made something crazy, didn't you?
-You'll see soon.
-Hey.
BUT WHERE'S THE OWNER?
Almost done.
My creation.
-Hi, we're back.
-You have a good time?
-Yeah.
-How are you? Exhausted?
MEANWHILE DEX PREPARES DINNER
PLENTY OF RICE
Let's start
by chopping the spring cabbage.
-What do you wanna eat?
-Bibimbap.
Spring cabbage bibimbap.
Oh, nice!
I love spring cabbage, let's do it.
LAST DINNER MENU SPRING CABBAGE BIBIMBAP
Hey, Dex, do you need any help?
Nah. Okay, first, we'll cut out the core.
Pop.
Then, we'll remove the dirty leaves.
QUARTER THEM SO THEY'RE EASIER TO EAT
SPRING CABBAGE PREP DONE
Now, for the sauce. Let's see…
MAKING THE SAUCE
ON THE VERGE OF OVERFLOWING
INTO A POT
MEASURING OUT THE SEASONINGS
I'll double the amount, I guess,
since it's a large portion.
HESITATES
TWO TIMES THIS AMOUNT?
AH WHATEVER
LOTS OF RED PEPPER POWDER
LOTS OF MINCED GARLIC TOO
SAND LANCE FISH SAUCE
SOY SAUCE X2
Done.
Then, mix it all together.
It's looking pretty good.
DEX'S GIANT BATCH OF SAUCE IS COMPLETE
THE RICE IS ALSO
ON THE VERGE OF OVERFLOWING
TASTING IN LARGE QUANTITIES TOO
Tastes good.
Perfect rice for bibimbap.
-Need help?
-I'm okay. It's fun, cooking like this.
Hey, are you totally exhausted
by this place?
Did I make it that obvious?
You're not alone.
Well, we're all leaving.
You really helped us out a lot.
Ah, it's my pleasure.
Dex, you'll leave in ten minutes.
Thanks! I'm just finishing up the dinner.
Please don't go.
It's almost done, so why don't I
explain it to you guys till then?
There's plenty of rice.
First, fill it with rice,
put the spring cabbage on top,
and put half a ladle
of this sauce I made on top.
Half a ladle.
Yeah. And then,
the fried eggs are made later.
-You put it on top like this, and done.
-Awesome, thank you.
I'd better get ready to leave now.
-Thanks, man. Have a safe trip.
-I will, and enjoy.
THE PART-TIMER PACKS HIS STUFF
Everyone, I just wanted to say…
I have to go home
after finishing this part-time job, sadly.
WHAT?
ALREADY?
NO!
-You're leaving, just like that?
-Block the door! Don't leave!
If the three of us hold him down,
he can't leave.
Tie him down!
It's hard enough already.
I'm sad to go, but I have to.
-Bye, man. Thanks.
-See you soon.
-Your work is inspiring.
-Bye, guys.
You're gonna have to let go.
-Yeon-koung, Zuha…
-We'll see you soon.
-So great to meet you!
-Wish you could stay longer.
-I'm excited for your dinner.
-You're the best!
-Hope you like the dinner.
-We will.
-On your way out, tell Kian to get back.
-Of course.
-Thanks.
-Close the door?
-Be careful!
-Thanks so much.
I'll miss all of you guys, for sure.
-Heading out? Oh…
-Yeah, I'm out.
-Great work.
-Wow.
SHOCKED
-Does it look scary?
-No, no, no, I think it's cute.
I honestly think it's done.
Wanna go in together?
-Aren't you leaving?
-I have to bring you in.
-Me?
-Yeah.
You can head out. I'm still working.
Well, it looks good.
Everyone wants you to come back.
What do you mean?
-They want to spend time with you.
-Oh…
-The urge to build never ends.
-But you need an intervention.
It looks great. That's enough.
THANKS TO DEX SNOWMAN-BUILDING IS OVER
-Did you have fun?
-I had such a great time.
-For sure.
-That's good.
Since he was constantly
bustling around and working,
it, uh, helped so much
to recharge my energy.
I was grateful that he came to help us.
I really appreciated the support.
-Careful, roads are slippery.
-Will do.
Later, Dex.
You know, both Kian and I, at our age,
it can be hard to find things or people
in life that make you genuinely laugh.
The experience was like a dream.
I think I'll remember it for a long time.
Goodbye, Kian's B&B!
THE PART-TIMER GETS OFF WORK
MEANWHILE, JUN-HO…
Okay, he wants me
to make some fried eggs for the last step.
So each person gets two.
STARTING THE TASK RIGHT AWAY
GOLDEN BROWN
FRIED EGGS COMPLETE
-Okay, all done.
-Did he finish cooking?
-I just did the last bit.
-Let's see. What time is it now?
-Not sure.
-Oh, shit.
I forgot you don't
have your watch. Hey, time?
FLICK
6:12.
-That late? Let's eat.
-Let's serve dinner.
-We should feed everyone.
-Let's get it down.
-You wanna go get it?
-Lower it down to me.
LOWERING THEIR LAST DINNER
-Wow, love it.
-Okay.
-Oh, and the sauce.
-Go slow.
-Rice?
-Hot?
-Hold the handles.
-Okay, thanks.
GROANING
Okay.
-Sesame oil.
-Thanks.
AFTERMATH OF PLAYING IN THE SNOW
-I'm tired.
-Good job, Kian.
-I think we're ready. Shall we?
-Everyone, let's eat.
Would it be all right if we ate outside?
-Of course. It's the perfect evening.
-Okay.
We prepared the tables and chairs for you.
Today, we're lucky
because Dex made dinner.
It's spring cabbage bibimbap.
Put some rice in your bowl
and then spring cabbage on top.
The sauce might be a bit salty,
so just mix in however much you want.
-Dig in.
-Thanks, Dex.
-I'm going easy.
-It may be salty for you.
-Just that much? Have more.
-Okay.
I should use the big bowl.
THE OWNER USES A BIG BOWL
Kian, that bowl matches your personality.
-Yeah? It's less messy.
-Uh-huh.
Grab your coats.
We're going out, dress warm enough.
Okay.
It's super cold outside
THE OWNER'S CHANTING IS CONTAGIOUS
We must put on our jackets
And hats and gloves
To go outside in the snow
Because it's cold as hell
We'll have to be careful
walking down. Don't spill the bibimbap.
-Here we go.
-Follow the owner.
Careful, guys.
We made the stairs
and everything. Head on down.
-You made this? That's so cool! Wow!
-Dex spearheaded the stairs.
Wow. What a creative idea.
I don't think we'd be able
to walk down here without them.
Oh, look at our snowman.
-It's awesome. Who made that?
-Looks good.
Is the one you made on the right or left?
-The left.
-Wow. That's super big.
-Have a seat over there.
-Okay.
PLOPPING DOWN ON THE GROUND
Wait, why did you sit there?
What? Oh, I just wanted you all
to pick your seats first.
Sit, guys. You can sit there, or there.
-That's a chair.
-We'll sit here.
-The chair feels stable, right?
-Yeah, it's great.
We made this.
We really had to pack it together.
EVERYONE IS SEATED
It started snowing.
Wow, so cool. It's magical.
-Yes, so nice.
-Isn't it romantic?
-Yeah.
-All right.
Vibes are even better
now that the sun's down.
-It's insane!
-Absolutely.
When else would we all do this?
Yeah. How is it,
doing this on your birthday, Hyeon-seo?
-This is the best birthday ever.
-It's fun?
-All right, enjoy.
-Enjoy the food.
-This is so cool.
-It's so delicious! Thanks!
Tastes so good.
Mmm…
Pretty good.
-Is it the bibimbap that's trending?
-People eat it all the time now.
A BITE OF SPRING CABBAGE
Is the sauce okay?
I think the sauce made the dish unique.
It wasn't just gochujang.
It had a special savory flavor.
PRECIOUS
I love the smell of the spring cabbage.
I agree.
-Dex did a good job seasoning it.
-He did.
I think I put too much sauce.
A MOMENT AGO
A LOT OF SAUCE
That may be really salty.
-Your rice is red.
-It's not spicy, but, yeah, salty.
Too much salt for you?
Don't suffer.
-Try mixing in snow.
-Huh?
Oh, true. If you add in some snow,
it'll dilute the flavor.
-Uh, okay.
-Seriously?
-Like salt, sprinkle it.
-I guess it won't kill me.
-Try a bit.
-Let's see.
SPRINKLING SNOW
-Are you guys sure?
-Like that, yeah. Now mix it.
Oh! I think it worked.
-Really? Cool.
-For sure. It tastes less salty now.
-Hey, do you want ramyeon?
-Yeah, that'll be nice.
Hey, everyone!
I have ramyeon for you.
-Looks good.
-Looks incredible, thanks.
-It might be a little undercooked.
-I'd never turn down ramyeon.
Wow, yes!
-Oh, enough.
-Okay.
Should I try the soup?
Oh, that's good.
PASSES IT TO THE OWNER
That hits the spot.
Hungry, huh?
AHHHH
-His whole face is covered.
-That warmed my stomach so well.
Ah, that's killer.
-I'm glad we did this. It's nice for them.
-Yeah. Love it.
-It's a nice vibe here.
-Exactly.
-Look at everyone sitting together.
-Talking, having fun.
We really wanted to make this vision
a reality. And we really did it. Wow.
We did good.
Good vibes.
We love good vibes.
Today is good vibes.
AFTER A DINNER WITH NICE VIBES
Everyone, feel free to go inside
whenever you want.
I'll wash those first.
YEON-KOUNG, ZUHA IN CHARGE OF THE DISHES
We, uh…
WE?
…just had our last meal.
It's crazy.
-Oh, wow.
-The final one.
We really worked our butts off, didn't we?
-Could you toss that out?
-Yeah.
CLEANING UP THE LEFTOVERS
There's a lot.
A LOT OF FOOD WASTE PILED UP
-Grab the food waste?
-Okay.
-We're gonna put it in the storage shed.
-But tie it up beforehand.
There's a lot.
HEAVY
How should we get this down there?
What? No!
What? No! No!
-No!
-I can't…
-This sucks!
It's awful!
-No, no, no!
-No!
What? What? What?
WHAT'S GOING ON?
-The bag broke.
-It burst.
Why? Oh, the smell.
Ah, the smell!
SOME GOT ON HIS FOOT
A HOT MESS
-Hold on a sec.
-What do we do?
-Let's see what we can do.
-You messed up big time.
LIMPING
Hold on. I need to wipe my feet off.
-Give me that.
-Go, go, go.
Yuck.
Something was rotten in there.
Well, at least,
it didn't explode on my head.
-Let's figure out what to do.
-Man. What are we gonna do about the mess?
Here, let me try.
Oh, it's inside the cracks.
SNIFF
WOOZY
A NEW PLASTIC BAG
-I'll go down and grab it from you.
-Let's be careful.
Okay.
Okay. Yes!
TRANSPORTING IT DOWN SAFELY
Gross.
WHILE THEY CLEAN UP THE FOOD WASTE
-Zip, zap.
-Zap.
-Zop!
-Zip, zap!
-Zip!
-Zap.
-Zop.
-Zip!
-Zap. Zip!
-Zap!
-Zop!
Zop!
THE OLDER MALES ARE EXCITED
ABOUT THE YOUNGER MALES' PUNISHMENT
Wanna do "Tell me"?
-Where are you starting?
-No music?
SHY
Now you guess.
-Two?
-Three?
-The kids are getting along.
-They love each other.
Let's clean up the kitchen a bit,
close it up for good.
-The whole thing?
-Yep.
ORGANIZING THE SEASONINGS
All right.
LINED UP PERFECTLY
THE OWNER PUTS AWAY THE CLEAN DISHES
Oh, man. Literally, all we do is clean.
-Goodness gracious.
-Man.
-We're in the home stretch.
-Man, oh, man.
-Come on!
-Oh, man.
Can we stop now?
-Looks good to me.
-It's clean enough, right?
KNOCKED OUT
Oh, I'm so exhausted,
I don't know if I can move.
WORN OUT
THE DISHES ARE DONE
-All done.
-We did it.
All right, we're done.
Great job, guys.
Isn't it kinda crazy to think
we'll be officially closed tomorrow?
-Especially for you, as the owner.
-Of course.
Yeah, it's bittersweet.
But, boss, you know what?
-Today is not even close to being over.
-I know I have to be grateful for it all.
-It's not over.
-The night is just getting started!
-It's just getting started.
-We'll party all night long.
We're gonna have a great night.
Let's focus on that right now.
Oh, man, screw this.
This is so freaking exhausting.
He's right.
I think there's a good chance I might die.
HIS TRUE FEELINGS SLIP OUT
Let it all out, Kian.
Hang in there a little longer.
It's almost over.
8:00 P.M.
I've been really eager to ask you.
How much do you practice every day
for your gaming?
On average, about 12 hours.
-Twelve hours?!
-Oh, yeah. Just about.
Isn't that a lot, though? For one day?
What time do you start in the morning?
-We usually start at 1:00 p.m.
-You start that late?
Yeah. So we start playing team games
from 1:00 to 4:00 p.m.
And then, we play team games
from 7:00 to 10:00 p.m.
And after 11:00 p.m.,
we will start our individual practice.
-You play till late, is that right?
-We do.
We go to bed around 4:00 or 5:00
in the morning.
So you really do practice
for the majority of your day.
That's right.
-Yeon-koung, can I ask you a question?
-Yeah.
How have you coped with slumps
in your career? If you've had them.
Oh, I've definitely had slumps.
When I was in my late twenties,
I went through a pretty intense slump.
I assume you started young?
-Since I was young.
-You're still young.
I started playing volleyball
when I was in fourth grade.
I was thrilled when I was selected
as a national team player.
But I started playing as a kid
because I liked it.
But once I started to feel the pressure
and it started to feel like a job,
it changed.
I lost the fun and fell into a slump.
-Oh…
-Like, "What am I doing?"
Like, "What?"
I was just going through the motions
at some point, you know?
Things can feel stagnant sometimes.
Yeah, I was so used to it all
that I forgot about so many of the things
that were important to me.
So whenever I go through something
like that where I lose track of myself,
I try to remember
why I started playing to begin with
and to feel that kind of joy again.
T1 is a really successful organization.
You guys are big, right?
-Yeah.
-The resolve you needed
when you first joined the team…
-There was a fire you had in you.
-For sure.
So maybe when things are feeling stale,
you can think back to that person
you were before
and how much you wanted to be
where you are now, you know?
-Most importantly, don't forget.
-Yeah.
-We started this because we like it.
-You're right.
-Our passion led us where we are.
-Passion, yeah.
And it still lives inside us.
That's why we do what we do.
-That's really well said.
-Yeah?
-Maybe I should start watching you play.
-Oh, really?
-I'll be rooting for T1.
-Oh, yes, please. Always.
Oh, my God. We have to make the cake now.
Okay, so…
WHERE IS HYEON-SEO?
RUSTLING
Today's Hyeon-seo's birthday,
so I wanted to make him a cake.
WITHOUT HIM KNOWING
-Cookies?
-Margaret?
We can add those.
-I think it's perfect.
-It's nice, right?
That's happening right now?
Live broadcast from Seoul.
TOTAL LUNAR ECLIPSE
-We can't see it from here?
-No.
I want to see it for real.
At least we can watch it here.
So, when the moon turns completely red,
that means that it's, you know, aligned?
Yes, and that'll be at 8:30.
BLOOD MOON
EARTH'S SHADOW COVERS THE MOON
AND MAKES IT GLOW RED
-We can all watch.
-We have experts here.
-Blood moon.
-Oh, look.
Should we make a wish?
-You want to make a wish?
-We should, yeah.
-It's a cosmic event.
-So we each get a wish.
Okay, ready?
-What the hell?
-Come make a wish.
Yeah, but hurry up.
KNEELING DOWN
-Come make a wish on a blood moon.
-What are you doing?
-Zuha, come here.
-We're praying.
-Praying? Okay.
-The eclipse started.
Let these guys get into good universities.
PRAYING FOR THE HIGH SCHOOLERS
All right, we have another thing planned.
Let's go outside.
-Should we go?
-Outside.
-Let's go first.
-I'll lead. Let's beat them out there.
JUN-HO GOES AHEAD WITH THE CAKE
Let's hide it behind here.
HE HIDES THE CAKE
We're going outside a lot today.
-The chairs. Take a seat.
-Okay.
SITTING DOWN
-Let's sit.
-Okay.
Come get one of these each. There you go.
Let's light candles and have a moment
for people to share their feelings.
Yeah, try to keep it lit.
That's it.
-Think everyone has one.
-Need yours lit?
-Are all of them lit?
-Yes.
Careful, everyone.
-Can you see any stars?
-No, but we might still.
Hyeon-seo, give me yours.
I'll take that.
But why?
VERY SUSPICIOUS
-Huh?
-For Hyeon-seo.
It's his birthday today.
Yeah.
-So instead of birthday candles…
-Uh-huh!
And one, two, three.
Happy birthday to you
Happy birthday, dear Hyeon-seo
Happy birthday!
-Happy birthday!
-Thank you!
-Happy birthday.
-Please dig in.
-You should have all of it.
-That's your cake.
-Happy birthday.
-Cheers!
Everyone, tonight is unfortunately
our final night.
And tonight, there's…
What is it, a red moon?
We're going to pretend we can see it
and make a wish.
So, for my wish,
it actually came true on this trip.
It was to meet Ms. Kim Yeon-koung.
So my wish for tonight is to pass
my teacher certification exams.
-You can do it.
-Good luck.
-All right.
-Thank you.
Ice climbing is a niche sport,
but there's rumors we may be
included someday in the Olympics.
Nice.
So my wish is for us to be
at the Olympics in 2030.
And I think you will. Yeah.
My goal is to become the world champion
in ice climbing.
-You'll have to take Young-geon's place.
-Sure, he can try.
-At least I'll give it a shot.
-You guys can be friendly rivals.
-Good one.
-Best of luck.
We have a League of Legends championship,
and we've won three years in a row.
I'm really hoping
we can win our fourth this year.
That's cool.
That's our goal,
we'll work hard to achieve it.
Yeah, I know you got this.
When you're stressed or sad,
looking up at the night sky can help.
That's why it's amazing.
And I hope you all can do that
and have fun lives. Thank you.
First, I'd like to share
something I've been thinking about.
So I've been doing what I do
for a super duper long time.
I've also experienced my fair share
of slumps and frustrations.
But I'm so moved by everyone's
different stories and passions.
Through getting to know you,
I'm leaving here inspired.
And I hope you know
that we're rooting for you.
We wish you health and happiness.
-That's so kind.
-Thank you.
I think I'm still trying to grow,
and I'm in the process of becoming
a better version of myself every day.
So my wish is for support on my journey
as I try to be the best person I can be.
Yes, hello. I'm Kim Yeon-koung.
Yes, you all know me.
After what felt like a lifetime last year,
I finally retired from being
a professional volleyball player.
And I spent a lot of my time since,
trying to figure out what I wanted to do
in my life and who I am
if I'm no longer an athlete.
And it's a big decision,
but I came to Kian's B&B
and I met a ton of people
from different walks of life
and listened to a lot of stories.
And it allowed me to learn,
organize my thoughts,
and you all gave me some perspective
outside of my life, so…
Since the boss told me to share something,
my wish is to find something
that makes my heart race this year.
Something that feels like how volleyball
felt when I first started to play.
So even if I don't find it this year,
now I know I want to keep looking
and keep discovering until I find it.
Whether I work in sports
or somewhere else,
I'll be passionate about it, approach it
with the same tenacity as sports and B&Bs.
Thank you all. Thanks.
-I feel like I'm going to cry.
-That's okay. You can.
I got a little emotional right there.
Oh, I feel…
I'm going to cry, guys.
Thank you all for sharing.
And I want to say, growing up,
I was never class president.
And I always felt my skills
as a leader were lacking.
But when we're here,
I feel motivated to do better.
-Was everything okay for you guys?
-Yes, it was awesome.
It was all right.
Well, I hope that
all your wishes come true
and that you never let a little snow
put out your fire for life.
And we have one last event for you now,
-if you'll follow me this way.
-What is it?
What are you doing?
And go ahead
and blow out your candles. All right.
Oh, wow.
-What's it gonna be?
-So much suspense.
Okay, to everyone who came to Kian's B&B
and to everyone who's been here,
not just today, I hope all your wishes
and dreams come true.
So we've prepared…
-this little button for you.
-Huh?
-What?
-A button?
Oh, my God. It's big.
A button.
A HUGE BUTTON
-Cool.
-We prepared an event
where all of you will press this button
and it'll work its magic on you.
So, uh, yeah,
your wishes get bigger and, uh…
Would you all like to press this button
at the same time?
-Yeah!
-Yeah? All right. One, two, three.
What happened?
FIREWORKS EXPLODE
OVER THE WHITE FIELD OF SNOW
That looks incredible!
I always wanted to have fireworks
on the last day, like we did in Season 1.
But if we just set them off,
it would've been like,
"Hey, enjoy the fireworks." That's it.
I wanted to make it feel like their wishes
were growing bigger and brighter,
just like the fireworks.
In Season 1, I pressed the button alone,
but I wanted everyone
to do it together this time.
A BUTTON TO PUSH TOGETHER
They're so pretty.
I probably won't ever get to experience
something like this again. It was so nice.
They were fireworks that would make
all our wishes come true.
It was a fantastic, romantic surprise.
It was so touching,
and I thought that was such
an amazing vision the boss had.
We're so close to them.
This is once-in-a-lifetime.
It was really special.
It reminded me of something
you'd see in a movie.
It was a nice gift
that helped us wrap up our trip
that was short and sweet, like a dream.
-Thank you so much!
-Best fireworks ever.
-Man, that was amazing!
-Such a magical vibe.
ONE MORE TIME
One more time.
Let's push it.
PUSHING IT AGAIN
Sorry, we can only press it once.
The budget's not that big.
Guess we have to recycle this too.
I can't believe
we saw fireworks that close.
Oh, shit.
Boss, I'll miss your slapstick comedy.
-That was a great surprise.
-Good.
-Best night ever.
-I'll remember it.
With that, everything we prepared is over.
-It was amazing.
-What did you think?
-Everyone loved it so much. Yeah.
-Really?
It wasn't much,
but I tried to make it as cool as I could.
It was cool.
When else in life are we going to see
fireworks that close and over the snow?
-They were a big hit.
-Yeah?
And it was nice
that we pressed the button together.
It felt like we were all doing
something meaningful together.
Is it cool that I'm turning off
half the lights?
9:30 P.M.
THEY TALK IN SMALL GROUPS
That's really great, like,
the fact that people
who are close to each other
can still compete
-with maturity and respect.
-And they cheer each other on.
Yeah, the fact that
you can do that naturally.
How is that even possible?
It's human nature to feel jealous,
even if it's your friend.
That makes sense.
But you guys compete
in a really healthy way.
-Yeah.
-That perspective is refreshing.
To be honest, I didn't know there were
this many lesser-known sports out there,
-like luge, ice climbing.
-Same.
-That's common.
-Yeah.
It's amazing that you're representing
our country as the best in the world.
Even without support.
Even if we try to promote ourselves,
it's such a lesser-known sport.
And the infrastructure is so small,
there's no support.
It's just tricky because
we're doing everything ourselves.
We try to do everything at once,
train, advocate for ourselves.
Then again,
if it does become an Olympic event,
we're hoping it opens
a lot of opportunities for the sport.
That makes a lot of sense.
That's why it's such an important goal.
I know how you feel.
I was so frustrated
when I was playing overseas.
-I was playing in Türkiye then.
-I haven't heard this story.
Back then,
I was sort of at the top of my game.
I was dominating everyone,
but because volleyball
isn't a popular sport,
I didn't get any press at all.
I was a top scorer,
but I didn't get any attention.
I felt unsupported during that time.
But luckily, after I went to the Olympics,
I got some recognition.
-But you're not getting that opportunity.
-That's right.
It's unfortunate.
As an athlete, I know how it feels
to be in an unpopular sport.
You're working so hard,
but no matter how well you do,
you still get passed over.
So I had a lot of empathy for their story.
They had to pay their own expenses,
even when they were going
to the world championships,
which they won.
It made me think about…
how much they've had to sacrifice
and what a toll that must have taken.
I found that heart-wrenching.
These guys are so hardworking
and talented.
I'm positive that good things
are coming their way.
-And maybe the Olympics.
-Yeah. Fingers crossed.
We'll be rooting for you.
We should probably go to bed.
We're going to sleep, guys.
-Okay, good night.
-Thanks.
-Sleep well, okay?
-Night, guys.
HYEON-SEO, SEONG-BHIN
AND YUN-WOO GO TO BED
Shoot. We never got to see you
use the karaoke.
So, like, do you just
go up there and sing?
-Can we use it?
-Sure, go ahead.
-Boss? Boss?
-Huh?
-What?
-He wants to sing a song.
Yeah, go sing a song, then.
ENTERING THE KARAOKE ROOM
-Going solo.
-I love that he's doing it alone.
It's nice, like there's background music.
Everyone's doing their own thing.
-We'll close this. Probably.
-Should we?
WITHOUT A TIME LIMIT
KARAOKE IS RUNNING AT FULL CAPACITY
They're really making the most of it.
Yeah, I'm glad
they're putting it to good use.
Cheers.
-Having fun?
-Yes.
How do you feel?
Can you believe it's the last day?
Yeah, well, I was feeling
sort of down in the beginning.
Why's that?
When I was younger,
I had fun meeting strangers,
but somehow it got harder for me.
Have you been disappointed by them?
No, I think I became numb to it.
Yeah, like, when it's your main objective.
From our perspective,
everything is shiny and new.
-Right.
-You're hosting for a long time.
Yeah, I think I just put a wall up.
It just takes me longer
to connect with people.
Anyway, with Kian's B&B, I was worried.
"Can I be genuine while meeting people?"
But I've never had
to fake any excitement on the show.
It's just, I'm giving it my all
and trying not to perform too much.
I wasn't sure if it was the right fit
for me to be a host on a show like this,
but as time went on,
I eased into it and felt more comfortable
welcoming people here.
HE GREW MORE AT EASE AS TIME PASSED
I just need to not get stuck in my head
and in the day-to-day,
and, you know, be more present.
But overall, I'm happy.
I should be having fun, right?
When I was younger,
I used to really love people watching.
Yeah, I just…
I had an interest in observing people
and wondering
what kind of lives they lived. But…
Yeah, I had a lot
of empathy and affection…
for my fellow human beings.
But as I've gotten older,
I think my curiosity for others
has kind of dampened.
Oh, man, why is this so hard now?
So I wondered, you know, "Have I changed?"
And even though I was taken aback
by the comment that I was serious or dark…
I realized something
because of Smita today.
Are you worried that you're coming off
as stressed out to the guests?
-I think so. I need to keep it light.
-Maybe.
It's nice to meet you, oh, yeah
Yeah
-Cheers!
Glad you're here.
Please enjoy yourselves.
Have fun before you leave.
But as I kept doing it over and over,
eventually I found…
Yeah, I was able to loosen up.
And it was really thanks to the guests.
I felt safer to come out of my shell
a little more each day.
It's so cold!
They were so understanding and generous
and let me open up.
You know, when I think about it,
I keep getting choked up,
just replaying it in my head.
The most important thing is,
I thought my heart had grown cold
or hopeless, but I think…
I was able to develop
some really genuine connections.
So as time went on,
that heart exterior cracked.
Trust me, Kian,
we like you and think you're social.
Oh, well, thanks.
You know, people actually do like me…
This just makes me blush.
All right, let's have a drink.
-Nice timing.
-Best of luck to everybody.
-Thank you.
-And to you as well.
Cheers.
I think I'm off to bed.
Have a great night, everyone.
-Going to sleep like that?
-Huh?
-Wash up first.
-I'll do it in the morning.
What, I'm just going to get dirty again.
You guys are crazy. You shower too much.
KIAN'S B&B
DAY 9
CLOSING DAY
CLEAR SKIES ON THE MORNING OF THE LAST DAY
KIAN'S B&B WINTERVILLE
3 HOURS BEFORE CLOSING
8:00 A.M.
JUN-HO'S THE FIRST TO GET UP
ON THE LAST DAY TOO
YEON-KOUNG AND ZUHA
ARE SLEEPING SIDE BY SIDE
THEY GET UP AT THE SAME TIME
THEY PUT AWAY THEIR BEDDING TOGETHER
AND PACK TOGETHER
Do you think you'll cry today?
Don't cry, Zuha.
THE BOSS IS PACKING UP TOO
HE PACKS THE TOWEL HE USED
I need new socks.
PUTTING ON SOCKS AFTER SMELLING THEM
HIS SUIT WORN AT THE PARTY
A SWEATSHIRT
AND A LONG PADDED JACKET
HE FINISHES PACKING ALL CLOTHES
FROM THE 9-DAY STAY
-You only got to enjoy it for half a day.
-Yes.
-Was it still fun?
-It was so much fun.
I'm so glad.
10:00 A.M.
It's already 10:00. Time to check out.
So it's time to leave.
I think it's over.
It is.
This time we're leaving with everyone.
-So it just feels like super weird.
-Yeah.
THE STAFF FEEL RESTLESS TOO
But sleeping in our own beds…
I'm excited, but sad.
Thank you guys for coming to visit.
Let's just all stay.
We don't want to leave.
-Yeah?
-We'll just move in.
All right, before you go,
we'll hang these up.
-Okay.
-For the last time, right?
SOMEWHAT EMOTIONAL?
Hard to say goodbye?
We'll try not to cry.
You can inspire them
by saying, "Be happy!"
Yeah, be happy. Uh…
Oh, be careful up there, guys.
Wow, you're working for us
right before you go?
-You can just throw them.
-Okay.
-We can pass the hangers down.
-Pull it all the way so it fits.
-Cool.
WORKING TOGETHER TO HANG THEM
-I'll help.
-I got it.
Teamwork, teamwork.
-Let's make it look good.
-Yeah, one sec.
Okay.
-Looks good, guys.
-Much better than on the floor.
Let's take a group photo.
Is the angle okay?
SETTING THE TIMER
-Are we all looking good, boss?
-Of course.
-It's on a timer.
-Okay.
-Quickly.
-Everyone, smile.
One, two, three…
WITH THE LAST GUESTS
Okay, we really have to go now.
I'll be rooting for you.
-I hope everything goes well.
-We had fun.
-Goodbye. Be safe.
-Thank you.
-Bye.
This place is challenging up to the end.
-Are we stuck?
-Snow's blocking the door.
Can we get out?
I think it's because the snow fell.
THE BOSS GOES OUT
I will not miss this door.
-We could bring the suitcases out.
-Oh, true.
THEY ESCAPE ONE BY ONE
-Hope to see you.
-Goodbye for real, guys.
-Thanks again.
-Time to go home.
-Goodbye!
-See you.
-Safe travels.
-Bye.
-Off we go.
The snow stopped
as soon as we had to leave.
Right? It let up just in time
for us to get home.
So, in ice climbing,
being the first person to step
on untouched snow is called "onsight."
Getting to play in the snow and have fun
made this trip
feel like a new start for me.
I didn't realize
truly how much I needed it.
I'm in love with that trampoline.
When you become an adult,
something so silly and fun
becomes a thing you don't do.
So I thought Kian's B&B
was like a playground for adults.
At a typical B&B, it's usually
easiest to do everything by myself.
But at Kian's B&B,
there were physical challenges
that made sure we worked together
and helped each other.
Out of all the guests
to visit this season,
we were the youngest by a lot.
But everyone older than us
was so thoughtful and kind to us.
I was able to forget about things
that stressed me out, like school.
And I got to have a ton of fun,
which was such an amazing experience.
It was only one night,
but it was so magical.
I'll remember it for a long time.
-It's one of my fondest memories so far.
-I think it deserves a ten out of ten.
-The house is even saying bye to us.
-That's right.
-Don't forget about us.
-Definitely keep in touch.
Okay.
THE LAST GUESTS CHECK OUT
The last guests have left.
-It was a good send-off.
-Let's clean up. One last time.
Fine.
-I'll sweep there.
-Okay.
-Then never again, thank God.
-So the day to leave is finally upon us.
THE LAST CLEANUP OF KIAN'S B&B
-Feels so weird, right?
-I know.
It's the last time
we're gonna see this place.
It's the last time I fold these.
Almost done. Almost done.
CLEANUP LIST
BREAK DOWN THE PULLEY
Yeon-koung? Sorry.
But can you hand me the snacks?
Be better if we leave them here.
CLEANUP LIST
GATHER LEFTOVER SNACKS IN THE KITCHEN
-Can you lift it?
-Yeah.
GETS INTO POSITION
-Now be careful.
-Is this smart?
Wait, wait, wait.
Can you lift this side up a bit?
Yeah, lift it.
-You got it?
-Slowly.
Okay.
-Nope.
-Oh, no.
Wait, wait, wait. Grab it.
-Okay.
-Grab it before it falls.
Shit.
A BIZARRE MESS UNTIL THE END
What a total mess, you guys.
Where's the dolly?
I already took it apart.
Oh, you did?
-Yeah.
-Try this. Here, here, here.
Can we use that?
Yeon-koung, I'm sorry, but…
-Can you put them in this, and lift it up?
-Oh, come on.
Wait a second.
Okay. Should have done that first.
-Thank you.
-Okay.
Ta-da.
THE KITCHEN IS NEATLY ORGANIZED
-Shouldn't we…
-I'll just put this box in there…
Do it together.
THIS TIME, THE BOX IS…
Are you okay there?
Can we help you carry that out?
STUCK
Don't pull so hard, you'll rip it.
BARELY ESCAPES
Oh, so how do we do this?
This would happen right at the end.
-It won't budge? Then just go.
-I can carry it out if I squish it.
-Here goes. Halfway there.
-It'll work, it'll work.
Oh, what the?
-Did it burst?
-You come out first, Jun-ho.
It ripped open.
It's okay, it's okay, it's okay.
-It's all spilling out now.
-To the very end.
PICKING UP THE FALLEN TRASH
Yeah, yeah, stupid door's annoying.
You can't check in now
even if you want to.
THEY SORT RECYCLABLES
FOR THE LAST TIME TOO
Is that all the trash?
I think we have all of it.
-I think we're done.
-Thank God.
THE LAST CLEANUP IS OVER
-We should write something.
-Sounds good. Let's all write.
Hey, what about the painting?
-Kian, your painting!
-Our mini Yeon-koung
Oh, man, it looks so weird
that your face is the only one up there.
Who cares?
-I didn't have time to do more. I guess.
-Will it be all right with just her?
JUN-HO & KIAN
-Kazuha wrote the longest message.
-For real?
"The people I met here,
the time we spent together…"
"They're truly precious
treasures and have changed my life."
Oh, she wrote that you're amazing.
KIAN'S B&B'S BOSS IS THE BEST!
Did you know she thinks that?
You're amazing.
HAPPY
-Zuha.
-Yeah?
Who told you to lie like that?
-Be real with him.
-She knows I'm not lying.
-Why doubt her sincerity?
-Zuha.
She's telling the truth.
-Do you need help?
-No, thanks.
-Let's go!
-Goodbye.
So long, B&B.
When I see the empty house like this,
it kind of seems like it flew by.
-Well, it's time to go.
-All right.
IT WAS GREAT MEETING SO MANY PEOPLE
THANK YOU FOR THE MEMORIES
BREAD UNNIE
We're heading out!
THANK YOU FOR BEAUTIFUL MEMORIES
GOOD JOB, EVERYONE
KAZUHA
I WANT TO THANK EVERYONE
FOR THE MEMORIES
JUN-HO
-To be going home?
-Uh-huh.
-The weather is beautiful.
-It really is.
It's so sunny.
Today's the best weather we've had.
Figures that it happens the day we leave.
Do we think the boss is…
-saying one last prayer inside?
-Praying?
-Hopefully, quickly.
-Oh…
Last time.
TURNING THE LIGHTS OFF FOR THE LAST TIME
Man, this is so weird.
REMEMBERING MOMENTS WE CAN'T GO BACK TO
KIAN84
With everybody gone, it just feels weird
to be cleaning up an empty place.
But once it was clean
and we were walking out,
I kept looking back.
I thought to myself,
"What if this was my actual home
and the people who came
were my real friends?"
I started to daydream
about that being true.
These kind of experiences
aren't built to last.
You know how flowers are the prettiest
when they first bloom,
but then they suddenly just wither away?
This place was kind of like that.
When I thought about
leaving this place for good, I…
felt like you do when you wake up
too soon from a dream.
This place taught me how to be present,
and also how to take an interest
in others.
After I retired, I was trying to find
my new purpose in life,
and I think I neglected the small joys,
friendship, rest, fun, travel.
I think I totally lost track
of what life is really about.
Oh, my God! This is fun!
But I reconnected with those
important things while at Kian's B&B.
Spending eight nights and nine days
welcoming guests here…
Yeah, that's the dream
that Kian kept talking about.
I was able to see that vision
shining through other people,
like a mirror almost.
This really was a precious experience.
Okay.
We may all be going
in different directions,
but meeting so many people
who do a lot of different things,
it was energizing
because they're all pros.
They're the best at what they do.
I kept thinking to myself,
"I should work a little bit harder
when I get home."
It went by really fast, but I loved it,
and I think it had
a really positive impact on me.
THE 2ND B&B IS CLOSED
-It's officially closed.
-Bye, house.
-No!
-Well, great work, everyone.
We did it.
-Now let's go.
-Let's get out of here.
-Oh, wow.
-We did it!
-Does it feel weird to be done?
-So weird.
-I feel like I have to come back tomorrow.
-Yeah.
And, of course, this walk is so long.
-Hard until the end.
-Guys, don't ever forget.
Hopes and dreams.
All right, let's get out of here.
I'll miss it here.
Let's try this.
But I'm really bad at it.
-Want me to hold the net?
-This net is great.
If we hit this ten times back and forth,
Kian's B&B will be a huge hit.
-Oh, please, I don't want to.
-Season 2 will be a huge hit.
But if we fail and the ball falls down,
then Kian's B&B will be in trouble.
-Hey, don't joke about that.
-And then we'll have to close down.
No, I'm kind of superstitious.
This is for the future of Season 2!
-Okay.
-Our goal is ten.
One, two, three…
You don't have to smack it.
-You have to do ten, okay? One, two…
-That's it!
Looks like we're in trouble.
-Hey!
-What?
Zuha, don't mess this up.
Let's give it a shot. No regrets.
-Two, three,
-That's it, that's it.
-four, five,
-Keep it up, guys.
six, seven, eight…
-nine, ten!
-Nine…
Hey, it's got to be underhand. No!
Nice try, though.
Hey, we have to do ten. We were at nine.
We have to do it. We have to.
Let's go, let's go.
-One…
-One, two,
-three, four, five…
-Three, four, five…
six, seven,
-eight…
-Eight!
Almost there.
Nine…
-Nine…
-Ten! We did it!
-Ten! Yeah, we did it!
Kian's B&B is going to be a hit.
Great job. You're good at that.
-All right, you did it.
-Sure did, boss!
That was so intense.
Good job.
By the skin of our teeth,
but we're going to be a hit.
-We will.
-We did it.